<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>umni&#039;s ramblings</title>
      <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on umni&#039;s ramblings</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Niche CS Games</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/cs-games</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/cs-games</guid>
    <description>This is a list of cool games related to computer science that you might not know about. Incredible proof machine Free to play: incredible.pm/ A game about proving things using intuitionistic logic.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:23:04 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>List of Knots</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/knots</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/knots</guid>
    <description>This is a list of simple knots, organized by use case. Meant as a reference for when you need a knot for something. Complicated rigging systems can easily be created by using multiple of these knots together.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Index.html</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/</guid>
    <description>Hi, I’m Alex! Known online as “umnikos”. I like math, programming, and everything in-between. What is this place? This is my “blog” where I’ve decided to write things.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 15:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>&quot;Do Not Find the Fox&quot; Game Variant</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/fox-game-variant</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/fox-game-variant</guid>
    <description>There’s been a “game” going semi-viral recently called “Do Not Find the Fox”. It’s pretty simple: You randomly select and place letter tiles, in order, and if you place all of them without ever spelling “fox” in any direction, you win.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Posts</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/tags/post</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/tags/post</guid>
    <description>These are the items that do not get significant edits after publication.</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 16:00:16 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Hamiltonian Cycle Problem</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/hamiltonian-circuits</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/hamiltonian-circuits</guid>
    <description> Problem: Prove that finding a hamiltonian cycle in a graph (a cycle that visits every vertex exactly once) is NP-hard. This is a well-studied problem with numerous different proofs.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quartz</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/quartz</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/quartz</guid>
    <description>Quartz is a static site generator, designed for digital gardening in an increasingly dead internet. I am just using it as the easiest (and laziest) tool out there for making a blog.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Browser Tab Notes</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/tab-notes</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/tab-notes</guid>
    <description>Lots of browser extensions[1][2] allow you to take notes inside of a new tab, but most of them store said notes inside local storage. This means that if you open multiple new tabs, all of them will have the same notes inside.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>