<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>umni&#039;s ramblings</title>
      <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on umni&#039;s ramblings</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>God Field Tutorial</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/godfield</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/godfield</guid>
    <description>God Field is a free to play flash game. It’s a dueler where you play cards on your turn until you’re the only one left standing. Rounds are quick, it’s mostly luck, and it’s a lot of fun.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>My Sidebery Firefox setup</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/sidebery</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/sidebery</guid>
    <description>Overview I have been using this cool new fork of Firefox for the last 6 months called “Sidebery”. It looks a bit like this It has all the usual features of Firefox, plus a few more: All of the browser tabs are on the side, can be organized hierarchically, and can even be colored.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>How I Began Journaling</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/simple-journaling</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/simple-journaling</guid>
    <description>I initially began taking notes because, before that, I was feeling overwhelmed. I seemingly had too many tasks and events to keep track of, and I’d constantly forget to do tasks even if it was the only task I had to do for that entire day.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>&quot;Do Not Find the Fox&quot; Game Variant</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/fox-game-variant</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/fox-game-variant</guid>
    <description> Update (2024-11-25) Alex Cheddar made a video on this exact variant where he showcases a simpler proof. There’s been a “game” going semi-viral recently called “Do Not Find the Fox”.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Hamiltonian Cycle Problem</title>
    <link>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/hamiltonian-circuits</link>
    <guid>https://umnikos.github.io/blog/hamiltonian-circuits</guid>
    <description> Problem: Prove that finding a hamiltonian cycle in a graph (a cycle that visits every vertex exactly once) is NP-hard. This is a well-studied problem with numerous different proofs.</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>